{"game_code":"2EY0A483","level_name":"qw","questions":[{"answer":"Data","incorrect":["Information","Files","Knowledge"],"question":"This is the basic building block of information, and it becomes meaningful when processed or interpreted."},{"answer":"It is raw and unprocessed","incorrect":["It is easily understood","It has meaning and context","It is processed and organized"],"question":"What is the primary characteristic of data?"},{"answer":"Information is derived from processing and organizing data","incorrect":["Information is always in a raw and unprocessed state","It has meaning and context","It is processed and organized"],"question":"Which of the following statements is true about information?"},{"answer":"Data communications","incorrect":["Data encryption","Computer programming","Graphical user interface"],"question":"The exchange of information in binary form between two connected devices, whether directly or through a network?"},{"answer":"Interfacing","incorrect":["Synchronization","Signal Generation","Recovery"],"question":"It is one of the communication tasks which refers to the need to convert the input data (digital) into a suitable form (analog) for transmission and vice-versa during reception."},{"answer":"Recovery","incorrect":["Signal Generation","Addressing and routing","Transmission system utilization"],"question":"It allows the system to resume an activity previously interrupted by an unexpected fault in the system. What communication task is that?"},{"answer":"Transport layer","incorrect":["Network layer","Session layer","Presentation layer"],"question":"Manages the transmission of data across a network."},{"answer":"Network layer","incorrect":["Application layer","Data Link layer","Presentation layer"],"question":"Handles addressing messages for delivery, as well as translating logical network addresses and names into their physical counterparts."},{"answer":"Data Link layer","incorrect":["Application layer","Network layer","Physical layer"],"question":"Handles special data frames (packets) between the Network layer and the Physical layer."},{"answer":"Network Interface Cards","incorrect":["Credit Cards","Pokemon Cards","Gift Cards"],"question":"An adapter card that plugs into the system bus of a computer and allows the computer to send and receive signals on a network."},{"answer":"Coaxial Cable","incorrect":["Shielded Twisted Pair (STP) Cable","Fiber Optic Cable","Unshielded Twisted Pair (UTP) Cable"],"question":"It is known for their ability to carry high-frequency signals over long distances with minimal interference. They are widely used for connecting cable television, satellite dishes, and in some cases, broadband modems to homes and businesses."},{"answer":"Fiber Optic Cable","incorrect":["Shielded Twisted Pair (STP) Cable","Coaxial Cable","Unshielded Twisted Pair (UTP) Cable"],"question":"They are known for their high-speed data transmission capabilities and are commonly used in long-distance and high-bandwidth applications, such as telecommunications networks, data centers, and internet backbones."},{"answer":"Unshielded Twisted Pair (UTP) Cable","incorrect":["Shielded Twisted Pair (STP) Cable","Coaxial Cable","Fiber Optic Cable"],"question":"These are prevalent in Ethernet networking, connecting devices like computers, switches, and routers. They are cost-effective and suitable for short to medium-distance network connections."},{"answer":"Shielded Twisted Pair (STP) Cable","incorrect":["Unshielded Twisted Pair (UTP) Cable","Coaxial Cable","Fiber Optic Cable"],"question":"These cables are often used in industrial and commercial settings where there may be higher levels of electromagnetic interference."}],"time":142}